- Bobby Darin singing
"Mack the Knife."
Let's have a nice hand for him.
(audience applauding)
(lively music)
♪ Ooh, the shark, babe ♪
♪ Has such teeth, dear ♪
♪ And it shows
them pearly white ♪
♪ Just a jackknife has
old Macheath, babe ♪
♪ And he keeps it out of sight ♪
♪ You know when
that shark bites ♪
♪ With his teeth, dear ♪
♪ Scarlet billows
start to spread ♪
♪ Well, fancy gloves, oh,
wears old Macheath, babe ♪
♪ So there's never,
never a trace of red ♪
♪ Now on the sidewalk, huh ♪
♪ Ah ooh, Sunday
morning, uh-huh ♪
♪ Lies a body just
oozin' life, eek ♪
♪ And someone's sneakin'
'round the corner ♪
♪ Could that someone
be Mack the Knife ♪
♪ There's a tugboat ♪
♪ Down by the river,
don't ya know ♪
♪ Where a cement bag's ♪
♪ Just a-droopin' on down ♪
♪ Oh, that cement is for ♪
♪ Just for the weight, dear ♪
♪ Five'll get ya ten, old
Macky's back in town ♪
♪ Now did ya hear
about Louie Miller ♪
♪ He disappeared, babe ♪
♪ After drawin' out all
his hard-earned cash ♪
♪ And now Macheath spends
just like a sailor ♪
♪ Could it be our boy's
done somethin' rash, whoo ♪
♪ Jenny Diver, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa, Sukey Tawdry ♪
♪ Look out Miss Lotte Lenya ♪
♪ Not to mention
old Lucy Brown ♪
♪ Oh, that line forms
on the right, babe ♪
♪ Now that Macky's
back in town ♪
♪ One more, one ♪
♪ I said Jenny Diver ♪
♪ Sukey Tawdry ♪
♪ Look out to old Lotte Lenya ♪
♪ And Miss Lucy Brown ♪
♪ Yes, that line forms
on the right, babe ♪
♪ Now that Macky's ♪
♪ Back in town ♪
(audience cheering)
♪ Look out, old Macky's back ♪
Thank you.
(audience applauding)
Thank you very much.
- [Ed] Good night, everybody.
Bobby, come back
here and take a bow.
What do you think
of this guy, huh?
(Ed laughs)